" There ain't nobody "
" Who can love me like you
Uh-huh! "
" I'm lost in your starlight
Yeah! "
" I keep fallin' through
Lost in your starlight "
" Oh, my mama said keep you away "
" You're a heartbreaker,
Soul shaker, love faker "
" Turnin' me on
You turn me on, babe "
" And I still want to stay
Hey! "
" There ain't nobody
There ain't nobody "
" Who can love me like you
Love me like you "
" Lost in your starlight
Lost in your starlight "
" I keep fallin' through, girl "
" Oh, my mama said keep you away "
" You're a heartbreaker,
Soul shaker, love faker "
" Turnin' me on
You turn me on, babe "
" And I still want to stay
Hey! "
" Baby girl, can I be honest? "
" Can I be honest? "
" You're trouble "
" The kind that everybody warns me about "
" But you know what "
" It's 3 in the morning
And I'm still thinking 'bout you "
" They say, I'm losing it "
" Maybe they're right "
" But I'm not complaining cuz... "
" There ain't nobody "
" Who can love this hard "
" Every kiss is fire "
" Every touch leaves scars "
" Ohh my sistas say
Keep you away "
" You're a heartbreaker,
Soul shaker, love faker "
" Turnin' me on "
" But I still want to stay "
" Ain't nobody "
" Who can love this hard "
" Love this hard "
" Every kiss is fire "
" Every touch leaves scars, Girl! "
" Ohh my sistas say
Keep you away "
" You're a heartbreaker,
Soul shaker, love faker "
" Turnin' me on "
" But I still want to stay "
Whatever happened,
it happened for the good.
What would follow be good,
is a philosophy doomed to fail.
What's happening at present,
and who's responsible for it
we eliminated whoever was in the way
and kept moving forward.
Suddenly, a voice was heard then,
and we questioned who gave them
the authority to decide for us.
That voice was of the Police.
To the Police, we're rowdies,
gangsters, and extremists.
If we won't fight for a boy's education,
what else is worth fighting for?
-Hey, old man.
-Yeah!
Too much workload, I believe.
You really consider this a motor?
The coil is entirely burned out.
If you strain it with so much workload,
this is what happens.
Instead of replacing a new coil
and a shaft...
buy a new motor.
Don't even get me started.
With no monsoon,
I've already lost everything I have.
Do something
and get this motor working.
-Oh, come on, Man.
-Who's this boy?
Is he your son?
Son?
He's a helper boy at my workshop.
Oh, oh! Hmm!
Neither do I have a wife.
Nor do I have a son to do my last rites.
I'm just sailing through my life.
Hey, Kanagu!
Put it on speakerphone.
Dad!
Please talk to me for a minute.
Didn't you say you don't have a son?
But I hear someone calling you father
over the phone.
They'll be here now.
Come on, hurry up!
Come on, quick!
Arasu Brother, come on, go ahead!
Come on! Come on!
Hand me your gun.
Hand me your gun,
if not, I'll freaking kill you.
Hand me the freakin' gun!
Hop on!
Das, hop in!
Come on, drive!
"Ready for the switch"
Hey, Kitty!
They seem like government guns.
It's got that heavy government stench.
Shut up, check the stash,
and offer your price.
So, you agree it's the government stash.
Hey!
Stop squeezing your brain.
You got the weapons you wanted.
Your master is well aware of us.
Shut up and leave.
Unnecessarily yapping--
Why are you getting worked up?
This is not some junkyard stuff.
We use it to kill people.
What if we get into trouble later?
In two weeks, I'm getting married.
Don't disappear
in the name of hiding out.
I've arranged for a lip-smacking feast.
You guys better make it.
Understand?
Hey, Saami, I will personally sprinkle
rose water on the wedding guests.
Enough?
-Hey, Saami!
-Are you happy now?
Brother!
Grab him and the stuff
and get out of here fast.
Here I come, Brother.
Don't forget to come to the wedding.
Can you believe it, Das?
Even Saami is settling down
with a family.
And Arasu Brother...
has a son who will carry forward his name.
Das, we should also look for
a suitable girl and get married.
I, too, desire to lead a life
with a wife and kids.
What do you say?
As if we don't have enough problems.
Shut up and drink!
He will never change.
Hey, Son, here you go.
Give this to your mother.
She's pissed at me and
walking ahead quickly.
Hand this to her.
Dad, does Grandpa also
address you as "son"?
I will tell you about it all.
You have one
and give your mother one too.
Mom! Mom!
I've been calling you.
Why aren't you paying attention?
Stop, Mom!
What do you want?
Why are you yelling?
Here, Dad asked me to give you
an ice apple.
I don't want it. You guys hog!
Come on, Mom.
Are you going to eat or not?
Give it back to that man.
I told you I don't want it.
Mom, why are you getting angry?
Why not? To your father,
the family isn't important.
He's always concerned about your education.
I wanted him to retain the property,
but he's set
on your English-medium education.
Do you think I don't care about you?
That doesn't mean
he can yell at me in front of people.
You can have all you want
and throw away the rest.
Dad, she doesn't want to
have the ice apple.
Fine, now tell me
why Grandpa doesn't visit us.
My dear Son,
your Grandpa will visit us.
Where else would he go?
Your Grandpa has a dispute with me.
That's it!
He will have to come to see
his handsome grandson.
He should come.
Dear wife! Dear wife!
It's a pride if our son studies
in English medium school.
Still six months left for the monsoon.
By then, the house would've
drowned in mortgage.
-It's scorching hot.
-Sir, why can't you give me a hand?
Hey, do you expect the SI to help you?
Pull out the barricades.
Hey! Who are you?
Sir, I'm Angani.
I'm from Thekkumalai.
Go and help him with the barricades.
Okay, Son, you go ahead with your mother.
I'll follow you guys.
Sir, please have some ice apple.
It'll help you cool down.
Sir, how did it happen?
How come someone stole guns
from the police themselves?
Hey, get going!
Okay, Sir.
Hey, what are you carrying?
Sir, it's for my son's education.
I sold all my properties.
And gathered 7 lakh rupees
to pay for his education.
I'm going to put him in
English medium school.
7 lakh rupees, you say?
When he's carrying so much money,
why would he indulge in these things?
Here, call your father.
I hope you're not upset
that I got angry.
We sold the land that fed us
to provide your education.
You must study well, Son.
I will study well.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'm scared
that he's carrying so much money.
Mom, I think his phone ran out of charge.
It says switched off.
With that much cash,
he should've come straight home.
Let's go before he spends it all.
Let's go!
Dad!
Hey, go further and check
if you can find your Dad.
Dear!
Dad!
-Dad!
-Dear!
Mom!
-Come over here.
-What is it?
Look over there.
It's been way too long
since we left him in the forest.
I don't know if he's even alive, Brother.
Don't cry, Mom.
On our way home, a Police officer stopped
and asked him to help with barricades.
That's the last I saw him.
-Now he has disappeared!
-Don't cry, Mom.
Oh, God,
I don't know what happened to him.
Hey, don't push!
Don't push, woman!
Get out of here!
I'm warning you! If you don't leave,
I'll book you under a brothel case.
Stop glaring at me.
Get out of here!
What was the last thing
your father told you?
Son, you go ahead with your mother.
I'll follow you guys.
Das, this is a Police matter.
We just stole the guns.
I feel let's not rush this in.
Why did you act in such haste?
What would've happened to my father?
That boy is clueless about
whether his father is alive.
Yet don't want us to rush in.
I will bring you the money.
In a way, we're responsible for this.
We must arrange the money.
Study the way your father
always wanted you to.
Sir, sir, please spare me.
Hey!
I have nothing to do with it.
Please don't harm me.
-Hey!
-Who the hell are you people?
Why are you doing this?
Please spare me.
Das, I feel they would've killed him.
We'll find out!
I don't know. I don't know.
Let go of me!
What did you do to him?
I don't know anything.
I'll confess! I'll confess!
I'll confess!
A kilometer from that spot.
A spot one kilometer from there.
I discarded him a kilometer from there
in the bushes.
Please spare me!
I made a mistake.
Kitty!
-I beg you for my life.
-Inform the family not to file a case.
Please spare me.
I made a mistake.
Money?
We split the money equally among us.
I called Arasu Brother.
He asked us to lay low
at Yuvaraj's Lodge in Chennai.
Come on, hurry up!
I hope you were briefed about everything.
Yes, Sir!
In one instance, a team stole
our department's discarded guns.
As it is, we're embarrassed
to reveal this incident.
In another case, the sub-inspector
who was investigating the case
was smashed by a hammer
and was brutally murdered
by being shot at close range.
Are these two incidents connected?
Who's behind all this?
We have no clue about it.
We did not issue an official statement yet.
If word gets out,
it'll tarnish our department's reputation.
Find out who murdered the inspector.
Be brutal!
Yes, Sir!
Four guys arrived at the spot.
-They arrived in two vehicles.
-What kind of vehicles?
An old Yamaha bike.
Another one...
I believe it was blue, Suzuki.
They were... wearing masks, Sir.
One of the guys... had curly hair.
It's that guy who shot him.
The others were chasing me down.
What kind of gun did he use?
The type we see in movies a lot.
Where they pop it out,
load bullets, and whirl it.
The one that holds six bullets.
What about the one who shot you?
It's the kind where you pull to shoot.
That kind of gun, Sir.
Yeah, that's the one!
You must stay put locally.
-If we need you, we'd call you.
-Sure, Sir.
" Malayla, Malayla "
" My mama, my body’s low fire "
" My mama, you’re slayin’
My trouble empire "
" Malayla, Malayla, move it for me "
" Malayla, Malayla, deeper you breathe "
" Malayla, Malayla, know when you need "
" Malayla, Malayla, dark energy "
" Dark energy... Dark energy... "
Brother, Arasu's men are here.
Arasu filled me in.
If you don't bring any trouble,
you could stay here.
Until you stay here...
you better shut up, your gob,
and stay put.
Understand?
-Mavattam.
-Yes, Brother.
-Keep an eye on them.
-I'll handle them.
Come with me.
The toilet is on this side.
If you need anything,
holler Mavattam.
Remember what my Boss mentioned.
Understood? I'm leaving.
-Mavattam!
-What is it?
-Just checking.
-Okay.
Look, bury your pride and
arrogance for a few days.
Even if someone spits on your face...
wipe it off, say sorry, and keep walking.
-Okay?
-Sure!
This applies to everyone.
Hey, where are you going?
I heard you, Bud.
Not to get angry
even if someone spits on you.
I won't get angry.
Karuppu, I'll rip your mouth out.
-He did you dirty.
-Why do you have to go down to drink?
-Hey, stop poking the bear.
-Hey, Das, I'm coming too.
One out of two troublemakers is sloshed.
I'll be happy if the other is sloshed too.
Go easy on him!
He's already upset
that his father is not talking to him.
" Relationships, an endless tale "
" Emotions, tales untold "
" Some stories never end "
" An ending
May still lead to another story "
" May all that follows be joyful "
" The burden your heart bears "
Devadas, please don't dwell on
what your uncles did to us.
Your focus should be entirely on education.
Hey! Who the hell are you?
-I don't care who the heck it is.
-Kitty, where is he going?
If you're a man, face me!
-Hey, who the hell are you?
-Here comes trouble!
Until the song ends...
[shushing]
Hey, Das!
Have you lost your mind?
Let's go!
Hey, let's go!
-Please continue singing.
-Hey!
-You leave. I'll bring him.
-You're testing my patience.
-You better bring him.
-Fine, you leave.
-Freaking mess!
-Das? Das?
We can listen to the song tomorrow.
Let's go from here.
Please get up.
Let's go!
Careful!
Keep walking.
Sir, that's a very old case.
You're saying it was 15 years ago.
I cannot dig up files so far.
It's difficult, Sir.
Sir?!
Sir, someone might notice.
-Please dig out the information.
-Just two minutes, Sir.
-Sir, he's back.
-Sir.
This is Arasu and his new team.
He came out of nowhere!
Gave him one tight slap!
Despite warnings,
your guy caused a problem.
Listen closely!
None of you should come downstairs.
Is he emotional about the song,
or does he have feelings for you?
They were high and acted in haste.
I'll handle them.
Fine, let's go.
Fine, Solo and I are going to the movie.
Wanna join?
No! I have to finish writing.
You guys carry on.
If you keep isolating yourself,
you'll go crazy.
-Sarah!
-Are you coming?
I wonder when you'll finish writing.
Why don't we go downstairs
to have a drink?
No freaking way, Dude!
Shut up and drink here.
Hey, he wishes to listen to a song.
Let him go. We'll manage it.
Hey, he's calm about it.
Why are you fueling him?
Are you his yes man?
You're hard to talk to.
Daily looking at the same faces
seems like we're already in a prison.
"O moon, don't come close to me "
" I'm not where you imagine me to be "
Hey, play your card.
" O moon, don't come close to me "
" I'm not where you imagine me to be "
" O flower, don't be enchanted by me "
-Hey, Das, where are you going?
-Dude, what happened?
-Get me a full bottle.
-You ruined the game.
" ...you imagine me to be "
-" O moon, don't come close to me "
-Shut up!
" ...me to be "
Where is he going?
Does he think we are all fools?
Das, her magnetic voice
is drawing you out, is it?
-Yeah, so what? Shut up and sit tight.
-Das!
Das, you caused a problem yesterday.
Please get back inside.
Let him go. He won't go far.
Hey!
Hey, If he causes trouble,
I'll slit your throat.
Let him go.
Always controlling everyone.
Are you looking for someone?
Are you short-tempered?
I saw you fighting yesterday.
Erm... that was my most favorite song.
After my mother's demise,
Dad used to play this song so often.
Moreover, that guy was interrupting
by talking over the phone.
So, I did it!
How long has it been
since your mother died?
Must be around 15-16 years.
Are you living here?
For a month now.
After that?
After that,
a new town and a new hotel.
And a different crowd.
But songs remain the same.
What about your family?
Why are you laughing?
Are you wondering why you would
share anything with a stranger?
You hesitate to tell the truth
to those you know.
But you can pour your heart out
to a stranger.
You're right!
I don't have to pretend.
So, tell me, stranger.
What about you?
I...
What happened, stranger?
Telling the truth is difficult.
You do what you love.
So, it's easy for you to share.
I'm doing something I don't love.
So, it's a bit difficult to share.
What makes you say
that I do what I love?
You smoke, you sing,
and you are having fun.
Why would you do it
if you don't love it?
This is a guise I wear to earn a living.
So, what do you love to do?
Nothing much, though.
I had a small desire.
Now even that has faded away.
Why? What happened to it?
Whenever I sing at a hotel,
I start to wonder, looking at the crowd...
One day without wearing this disguise...
I wish to come as a guest
and enjoy listening to someone sing.
That's it. Nothing else.
Then come over tomorrow
and give me company.
The braided girl did sing well.
Let her take over.
I'm serious about it.
Please join me tomorrow.
No need.
It'll become an issue.
Please hear me out.
The owner of this place is known to me.
You hang out with me tomorrow.
Take a day off.
Hey, what are you doing for so long,
damn it?
Get back!
I don't know your name,
and you don't know mine.
We will not get familiar.
And it's not required.
What was that you said?
Ah... strangers!
We'd stay strangers!
But please hang out with me tomorrow.
You are coming!
Only a week is left
for the sister's wedding.
We still haven't started
sending out invitations.
Are you listening?
I'm not able to
handle everything alone out here.
Please handle it.
I have spoken to my senior.
-I'll be there soon.
-Sir! Sir!
Either fix your phone
or fix your family.
Always on speakerphone
with annoying problems.
If you don't make it,
people will talk.
He is Arasu, an ex-police officer.
15 years ago, for supplying
discarded guns to the naxals...
he was arrested and locked up in prison.
There he met...
Das.
Sebastian.
Karuppan.
Kitty.
He formed a team with them
and escaped from the prison.
And have been operating as a gang to date.
How are they related to this case?
We investigated an eyewitness in
the recent inspector's murder case.
His description perfectly matches theirs.
Keeping Arasu's history
and the current armed robbery in mind...
followed by the inspector's murder,
and eyewitness's statement.
From all this, I have a hunch
that they're behind all of it.
Okay.
Quickly finish up the investigation
and update me.
Thank you, Sir.
Hey, shall we go?
I have a slight headache.
Could you manage alone today?
It doesn't look like you got a headache.
Still, I believe you.
Fine, just for today.
Take care!
You came!
I thought you weren't coming.
Headache? I'll handle you later.
Come on, relax!
Would you like to have a drink?
No.
What are you doing over here?
Hello, over here!
One PSOP.
I'm speaking to her, not you.
Why not ask me?
One PSOP.
-And you?
-No...
-Shall I make it two?
-No, apple juice.
Hey, ice cubes.
" Silent tunes find their voice "
" Your breath lingers with mine "
" Moonlight drizzles softly "
I'm leaving!
Hey, what is it?
Are you going to feed her?
I'll call you if I need anything.
Please sit down.
" The scent of love surrounds us "
" Even my breathing has changed "
" La La La lost in your hangova "
I reckon there's a story behind that scar.
Go ahead, say it, stranger.
" La La La lost in your hangova "
" So lost in your hangova "
I was born and brought up in Coimbatore.
Since childhood,
listening to film songs, I loved singing.
I took singing classes and learned to sing.
When I was young, my sister went missing.
Ever since then, my parents
barely let me leave the house.
Still, I made it to Chennai
to pursue singing.
I arrived in Chennai
and met a music director
dated him,
and eventually,
I got into a toxic relationship.
I now despise singing.
Now, whenever I sing...
a part of me dies.
" You're my hangova! "
No, I quit!
Until today,
I haven't spoken much to anyone about it.
At least you felt like talking today.
Will that girl sing anything we request?
What song do you want?
Ask her to sing
"Chakku Chakku Vaththikuchi."
You still haven't touched your drink.
" Your breath lingers with mine "
" Moonlight drizzles softly "
" Stretching the night beyond "
" Your lightning glance grazes me "
" My body awakens within "
" The scent of love surrounds us "
" Even my breathing has changed "
My Mother.
" So lost in your hangova "
How?
What do you mean?
What gave you the courage
to speak to a stranger?
It's courage that stems from anonymity.
Oh!
Not what I meant exactly.
Like you mentioned earlier.
We can pour our hearts out to a stranger.
Hey, I thought you were unwell.
Are you coming back or not?
" ...lost in your hangova "
Thank you!
" So lost in your hangova "
-Did you hand in your resignation?
-I can hear you.
-Fine...
-This man, I say.
Bhojraj, Sir, your bag.
I am leaving your bag here.
-Please inform them soon.
-Sir!
It'll take 9 hours
to arrive in Sathyamangalam.
Whatever you want to speak,
get it over now.
-Don't torture us during the travel.
-This Man, you mean?
" O moon, don't come close to me "
-Hey, Das...
-What a croaking voice!
you don't enjoy our singing, right?
What do you say, Sebastian?
Welcome everyone.
I sense incoming trouble.
How come the centerpiece is accompanied
by the right and left hands?
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
Can't you guys keep it quiet?
Brother, what is it now?
We did not come to prison.
To be controlled by rules.
We're not troubling anyone.
Are we?
We're just being ourselves.
Brother is either way paying you.
-Let it go, Brother.
-Oh, money?
Just because you're paying,
would you shit on my face?
Brother, why would you?
Why would you talk like this?
I'll slit your throat, damn it.
Hey, bring it on!
Freaking Arasu!
Hey, Das!
Das!
Das, take him out.
Don't spare anyone.
Hey! Hey!
Das, what the hell are you doing?
Stop it!
Damn, this guy, I say!
Take him out, Das!
Kill him, damn it! Die!
Kill him!
Das, don't spare him!
Das, watch your back!
Hey, don't spare him.
Kill him.
How dare you guys?
-Kill him!
-Hey, let go of him!
Hey, don't stop him, damn it!
Please listen to me.
Hey, let go of him!
Hey, come over here.
I'm going to kill you.
Let's go! Let's go!
-Das!
-Calm down and hear me out.
-They swore at you, too.
-You keep walking.
Hey!
Brother, I can't take it anymore.
They don't listen to me.
You relieve me.
I'll be on my way.
Let's get out of here.
-Damn it!
-Yes, Brother.
Fine, I'll speak to them.
Dude, please calm yourself.
Guys listen!
Arasu Brother called and said
he would handle the matter.
-He asked us to leave from here.
-Let's go, guys.
Hey, Das,
Arasu Brother has spoken...
-Let's go now.
-Trust me, Arasu called me.
You don't have to listen to me.
But you respect his words, right?
He asked us to leave.
So, let's leave.
Sir, we have information that Das and his
team are hiding at the Happy Days Hotel.
-Source?
-Hotel owner, Yuvaraj.
Kitty, let's take the bike.
Hey, let's ditch the bike.
We'll take the bus and go to the spot.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, Das.
-Hey!
-What is it?
Come here.
What now?
You guys go ahead.
I'll meet her once.
Dude, it doesn't feel right.
Let's leave from here.
Hey, what's his problem now?
Hey, I'm not going to cause trouble?
I don't know
if I'm going to see her anymore.
Let me meet her once.
You go ahead.
Hey, he'll never change.
Are you coming with me or not?
Kitty, how can we leave him behind?
Fine, wait a minute.
-What now?
-There's blood on you!
Make it quick!
Sir, he's upstairs!
You guys spread out.
-Go!
-Sure!
Please wait a minute.
I don't know why I even spoke with you.
-Please hear me out--
-I don't want this!
-Let's remain strangers.
-Please hear me out.
One minute, hear me out.
I got him! I got him!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Come on!
Sir, sir, I think we shot a girl.
Detain him alive.
Hey, search all the rooms.
Go downstairs
and catch the rest of the team.
No!
Hey! Hey!
" Eyes, don't fade away "
" The solace of your shadow... "
" Let the silence linger "
" As if I were your breath... "
-Hey!
-Who is this girl?
Sir, she's a bar singer.
Her name is Parvathy.
No substantial background.
You can easily register her under any case.
" Bound to your eyes,
Your heart, and your breath "
-Rajarishi.
-Sir.
Sir, sir, she's still alive.
Sir, let's take her to the hospital.
-Tell me, Sir.
-Sir!
-Sir...
-In-and-out injury.
Bullet must be somewhere here.
-Look for it.
-Okay, Sir.
Sir, let's take her to the hospital.
Let's take her to the hospital.
Sir, she's still alive.
We can still save her.
She's still breathing.
She's still breathing!
The girl is still alive.
Let's save her.
If we take her to the hospital,
will you be answerable to Human Rights?
" The solace of your shadow... "
She's still breathing!
[Moondram Pirai playing on TV]
Hey, Chandra!
The customer has arrived.
Get ready fast.
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" Bu... Bu... Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" I came with the pressure on "
" Too much weight still I move on "
" White hair on the dashboard blow "
" But I keep my face cold "
" You talk big but you fall flat "
" I don't think I just run that "
" Whole room shift
When I step through heavy a lot "
" When I go through "
" You talk big but you fall flat "
" I don't think I just run that "
" Whole room shift
When I step through heavy a lot "
" When I go through "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
Where have you stashed the weapons?
We must find out the details
about the weapons.
Instead of wasting time on him...
use this as a lead
and trace out Arasu and team.
Okay!
Let it not be a lockup death.
Be careful.
Hey, Saami, what happened to Das?
Arasu Brother called.
Police arrested him.
-What are you saying?
-He went to see the girl upstairs.
That's his fate. Move on!
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" All night, no pause "
Why did you hide it from me?
You knew she was pregnant.
Hand me the cover.
Don't worry.
Hereafter, you can never get pregnant.
Hold the fetus.
Silk!
How many more days?
I'm going mad!
Any update on Das?
" I came with the pressure on "
" Too much weight still I move on "
" White hair on the dashboard blow "
" But I keep my face cold "
" You talk big but you fall flat "
" I don't think I just run that "
" Whole room shift
When I step through heavy a lot "
" When I go through "
" You talk big but you fall flat "
" I don't think I just run that "
" Whole room shift
When I step through heavy a lot "
" When I go through "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
Once again, if any girl tries to run,
I'll slit their throat.
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" We go up We go off "
" All night, no pause "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga"
" We go up We go off "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" All night, no pause "
Kitty, I feel very suffocated.
Let's step out for a while.
Give me a pack of cigarettes.
Kitty, anything else?
Hey, the police are here.
Karuppu, let's scoot.
-Don't run.
-Fine, walk faster.
Walk faster!
-Hey!
-Karuppu, run!
-Kitty, keep running.
-Run, everyone!
It's the department pistol, Manoj.
We'll trace it out, Sir.
Run, Karuppu!
Hey, this way. This way.
Hey! Hey!
Come on, Kitty!
Don't stop!
-Come on, run!
-Hey!
[overlapping yelling]
Hey, your gang member Sebastian is dead.
Better confess the truth.
If not, you're next!
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
" We go up We go off "
" All night, no pause "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
Sir!
It's the gun we recovered when we caught
Das's gang member Sebastian.
As I suspected, it's the same team
that committed both crimes.
-What happened to Sebastian?
-They shot him dead.
What is it, Kitty?
Did they kill him?
I'm looking for Yuvaraj.
Brother, we're running for our lives here.
Seeking out Yuvaraj is not important now.
He's the dog who snitched on you guys.
Do as I say.
Until I call, stay put.
That means Das is useless for us.
Yes, Sir.
He's not speaking a word.
Shall we produce Das in court then?
-Sir, we will--
-Bhojraj, a girl died.
You caught another member
but shot him dead.
The court's 15-day deadline has ended.
I'll take him out using another team.
" Drop the beat! "
" One who stands alone,
Without prejudice "
" No one in the world
Can hold him back "
" Without shield, armor, or an army "
" He smoked away every enmity "
" Bum Baa... Bum Baa Diga "
" Bum Baa Diga "
" Without prejudice "
" Can hold him back "
" One man army "
" Tham tharikida thithithom,
Murugan's battle cry resounds! "
" Dhim tharikida thithithom,
We defied the world on all sides "
" Tham tharikida thithithom,
Murugan's battle cry resounds! "
Brother, this is Das speaking.
Where are Kitty and Karuppan?
They're hiding out
at Kitty's brother's place.
Ask them to break
and throw away the SIM cards.
" Bum Baa... Bum Baa Diga "
" Bum Baa Diga Diga "
What mess have you guys created?
If Kitty had gotten married,
he would've fathered two children.
Just because I'm his brother
I am living my life on edge.
How long do I have to endure
this Police torture?
For the past three days,
they've been hiding out here.
I managed to convince my Boss.
He's been rambling about going to Andhra.
Das, ask him to stay put,
and I'll take care of him.
At least he will stay alive.
They've killed your friend Sebastian.
They shot him dead.
I'm scared now.
Please make him understand.
Come with me.
Das, we should also look for
a suitable girl and get married.
I, too, desire to lead a life
with a wife and kids.
How did you leave Sebastian behind?
They killed him, Das.
Yuvaraj snitched on us.
Bhojraj and his team shot him dead.
We must shoot them, Das.
We must not spare even one
we must shoot them all.
Hey, moron!
Stop fueling him and sit quietly.
Hey, he's not freaking fueling me.
I'm going to kill them all.
Yeah, Bhojraj is waiting
so that you can kill them all.
If you keep going head on
we'll be dead in no time.
Hey, Kitty! They killed our brother!
Yet you want us to spare them.
When you escaped
why didn't you go away?
Why the heck did you come over here?
We must deliver the money.
How could I abandon it?
Let's drop everything, go to Andhra, change
our identities, and live a reformed life.
My dear brother, it's enough that
you think of living a reformed life.
You don't have to go to Andhra.
Shut up and stay put.
I will look after you.
I can't stay here.
They won't let me live in peace.
Enough with the melodrama!
First, we must shoot Bhojraj!
Damn it!
But before we do that,
we must shoot that rascal Yuvaraj.
What did he say
he would do to Sebastian?
I will slit your throat!
Now, you're talking, my friend.
We're slitting his throat!
We're slitting everyone's throat.
We're doing it!
Yuvaraj is hiding out here.
-Fine, you may leave.
-Okay, Sir.
-Yes, Brother.
-I tracked down Yuvaraj.
Sait is sending his man
go with him.
TN 33C 2124
Red color Omni.
Hey, isn't this Sebastian's shirt?
-Not that important.
-Yes! Don't remind me of it.
-Is he truly a Sait?
-How would I know?
Arasu sent him.
Even after looking at his attire
he doesn't come across as a Sait.
Who's Kitty out here?
That doesn't matter.
Who are you?
Hey, I'm the one Arasu sent.
-Name?
-Chunnilal.
Hurry up and get inside the car.
We must leave before dawn.
The police are on the lookout.
[in Hindi] Let's go!
They let him escape!
He could've let us execute the encounter.
Once again, we must start from scratch.
-Das's father lives in Vellore, right?
-Yes, sir.
-Put him under surveillance.
-Sure, sir.
Dad, when are you coming home?
Please come home soon.
Don't you feel like
coming home to see us?
I'll be home, Dear.
Please tell Mom.
You must make her understand.
I get the feeling someone in our department
has helped them execute this robbery.
No, Sir. We can't proceed in that
angle without any solid evidence.
If we still proceed, we'll be in trouble.
Sir, Banglapudur is on that side.
And on this side
Gobichettipalayam G2 Police Station.
There's confusion about which
jurisdiction this bridge falls under.
That's why they're dragging this case out.
Great, another pickle to handle.
-Vehicle entry point?
-From this side, Gobichettipalayam.
Even the file states the same.
-Inform the station.
-Sure, Sir!
-When will you come home, Dad?
-I'll talk to you later.
Dad!
Sir, I...
Sir, I'm planning to resign from the job.
Sir, I want to spend some time
with my family.
Please!
Family weakness.
Why the heck
did you pick this line of work?
Either you should've stayed single like me.
Or else you should've married someone
who understood you and your profession.
You didn't do either.
Moreover, you had a child.
And keep nagging me
to go and see them.
What's this behavior, Ashraf?
Sir, Sir, we should've... saved that girl.
Collateral damage!
We'll seek confession.
-Manoj!
-Sir!
Who got posted here
after the armed robbery?
You both may go and do your duty.
Go!
Those who were not present on duty
during the armed robbery?
You may leave as well.
Why was no local security assigned
to the weapons truck?
I was on a different duty
on that day, Sir.
It was Arokiadoss on duty.
You may go.
Please come.
Come!
-Sir!
-Your name?
-Arokiadoss, Sir.
-Arokiadoss!
Yes, sir.
-You do look fit.
-Sir!
Do you know Arasu?
I don't know him, Sir
Fine, forget it. Not important.
Now, tell me.
Sir, Murugavel, sir
assigned the patrol vehicle.
And asked me to follow the truck
with three other officers.
So, you're saying only you knew
the truck's route and time.
Yes, Sir.
It was Murgavel, Sir, who asked me
to write down the timing details.
I noted it down.
The details about the truck
known exclusively to you
how did Arasu and team came to know?
Sir!
I don't like it that you're questioning me
at my own station like I'm an accused.
-Bhojraj is a Police officer.
-I get it, Brother.
Let's not mess with him at the moment.
Forget about that.
What happened to the money?
I spoke to Saami
and made all the arrangements.
Your priority is to kill Yuvaraj.
You don't worry about Yuvaraj.
He's as good as dead now.
We're here to surveil the place.
We'll kill him by tomorrow.
Sait will help you guys cross the border.
Arrange the money for Angani's family
and safely cross the border.
Hey, give me a cigarette.
Welcome, Arasu, sir.
All your activities
are against the Government.
But the irony is your name,
Arasu (Government).
Are you mocking us?
Do you recognize him?
He's your informer!
Despite giving you severe
shock treatment all over your body
you still managed to father a child.
Kitty, Das, and Karuppan.
Where are these guys?
So, please be good and tell me the truth.
Hey, hot head.
I've spoken to them.
Go ahead.
You're going to do the deed.
So, be safe.
Hey, your client is coming.
Hey, Brother, is it your first time?
But you don't look like a first-timer.
Your face is scarred
like you were in a fight.
You do look like a rugged guy.
Where are you from?
You don't seem like you're from here.
Listen, my girls are top-tucker.
Top class, you know!
The clients don't easily get over them.
If you're going to be stubborn about
not leaving, I'll cut your hands.
Hey, quickly finish the game.
Quickly finish it.
Listen for one time, it's 1,500 rupees.
We follow strict rules.
I don't mind if you treat her roughly.
If you want to go again,
then you will be charged another 1,500.
Nothing is going to happen tonight.
I was born and brought up in Coimbatore.
When I was young,
my sister went missing.
Are you from Coimbatore?
Why? Would you prefer
only a girl from Coimbatore?
Just answer the question.
Hey, please don't irritate me
during my bedtime.
Tell me!
Come on, tell me.
Oh, God!
When I was 6 years old,
they brought me here from Calcutta.
I've been in this room for 18 years now.
18 years, you say?
You're right!
Did you say Calcutta?
Yes, what about it?
But you speak Tamil.
Tamil, Telugu, Malayalam,
Hindi, Kannada, Bengali...
I speak all languages.
You say you never left this place for
18 years, yet know so many languages?
Right here, on this bed!
Are you here willingly?
Yeah, I am.
I pray to sleep with 10 people in a day.
If that isn't enough,
did you notice the boys outside?
The dogs who are playing carrom board.
Rape me often and record videos of it.
I prayed for this to happen as well.
To top it all,
the guy who brought you here...
That midget rascal you know...
Did it never occur to you
to visit your family in Calcutta?
It's my family who sold me to these devils.
Are you going to do the deed or talk?
This man makes so much money
but rides in an auto.
He won't spend!
He won't spend a penny.
Das, he has arrived.
Be ready.
Hey, just do a recon.
I've been in this room for 18 years now.
Rape me often and record videos of it.
Family is always a weakness.
You can find them
at SR Wedding Hall in Erode.
They're hiding out there.
Can I trust your word?
Armed gangster!
Today,
I'm going to end your reign for good.
Son, come with me.
Ma'am, you come with me too.
Shoot!
Bloody shoot me!
Hey, Chunnilal, start the car.
Das, let's leave.
He is here until tomorrow.
What happened?
All okay?
Come on, get in.
-Hey!
-Das, are we doing it today?
-Are we taking him out tonight?
-What are you doing, Das?
Shut up, you moron!
Why are you yelling at me?
Hey!
-Hey, don't stop him.
-He's going to cause major trouble.
Hey!
-What are you looking for?
-Wallet.
Hey, would you like to play the board?
-Hey, check what's happening out there.
-Hurry up!
Dad! Dad!
No substantial background.
You can easily register her under any case.
Stop right there.
Where are you running off to?
What happened inside?
Who are you?!
Take away all the girls and leave.
Come on, let's play the board.
Everyone, come upstairs!
-Where are they running to?
-I think there's a problem upstairs.
-Hey!
-Why are so many people running?
-Hey, damn it! Let's go.
-Oh, no!
Hey!
Hey, Kitty!
Hey, don't spare anyone.
Shoot them all.
-Hey, run away, or else I'll shoot!
-Shoot everyone, Kitty!
Shoot everyone!
I'll handle them.
You, bring Das.
This is how I know the play board.
Hey, Das, what have you done?
This wasn't the plan.
Hurry up, now.
You keep the engine running
I'll come.
Damn, this guy!
Is he the one
who kept you locked up in here?
The other girls escaped.
You, too, leave.
Das!
Das, hurry up!
Come on, Das!
Hey, who's that girl?
-Hey?
-Hey, wait!
Didn't I tell you to go away somewhere?
-Why is he speaking to her?
-Das, who is she?
I told you to leave!
I don't know where to go.
-Hey, why are you indulging her?
-I freakin' know. Shut up!
I know!
I don't know where to go.
Come with me.
I'll drop you off somewhere safe.
We're not safe ourselves
and you're offering her safety.
Hey!
Hey, Das, bring her quickly.
-Why are you encouraging him?
-Hey, stop yelling!
-Why are you guys always fighting?
-Get inside the car!
-First, bring that chick with us.
-Hey, Chunnilal, I should throw you out.
You get in, and we'll help you.
Hey, girl, stop gazing and get inside.
-Das has already agreed.
-You guys are inviting trouble.
Listen, we have no time.
Are you coming or not?
Hey, Das has already agreed.
Get inside the car.
Hey, get inside the car!
Get in!
Get inside! Start the car!
We're already neck-deep in danger.
I don't know how to explain this to Arasu.
Hey! Hey!
Look over there.
The girl you brought along might die.
Bring her back!
Thanks!
For what?
You hesitate to tell the truth
to those you know.
But you can pour your heart out
to a stranger.
Anyone who I've been with
will share their stories with me.
I, too, used to share my story with them.
Half our clients are Police.
They are well aware of
what's happening out here.
That they've locked up girls
and are running a business.
Yet no one cares to help.
So, I thanked you.
Why did you come back?
They killed my mother
when I was very young.
So, I killed them and was in prison.
So, I know what it's like
to be locked inside 4 walls.
I thought about it and came back.
I was afraid
that I would never experience nature.
Why?
When a woman turns older,
around 38-40 years,
they kill them by poisoning their food.
And discard their body somewhere.
Why are you stirring up old stories?
Now, you're out of that hell.
So, find a way to live a good life.
I thought they would let me out
when I turned 12.
I, too, wished to get married
and have children like anyone else.
Later, that wish disappeared.
Why? Did all the men in the world die?
You can still get married and settle down.
Don't bother about me.
Who are you, people?
Do you have a father?
It's not like I'm God.
I do have a father.
Does he not live with you?
He knows that he won't be safe
if he lives with me.
That's why he's away from me.
Doesn't it occur to you to see him?
Are you asking me
the same question I asked?
Go and rest well.
I'll find a way
to drop you off somewhere safe.
Oi!
My name is Chandra.
What's your name?
Devadas!
Arasu Bro is not answering my calls.
And he's oblivious to the issue at hand
and brought her along.
Hey, Kitty, we're in the middle of nowhere.
And you're saying
he's not answering your call.
As per the instructions I got,
we were supposed to be at the wedding hall.
Okay, okay.
Hey, Kitty, pass me the bag.
At least there are 50 SIM cards
in this bag.
So, they've been switching
SIM cards once every two days.
I'm sure not a single card
is registered in Arasu's name.
Anyway, trace the last SIM card
he used to call.
For whatever it's worth.
Hey, I'm surprised you're getting married
at your age.
Hey, Kitty, I agree with what you said.
So we, too, have a chance in life.
Yeah, I will be there.
As you mentioned, we'll go to Andhra,
find a girl, and get married.
-What do you say, Kitty?
-Hey, Karuppu, shut up, dude.
Instructions are to leave in the morning.
So, you guys stay right here.
I'll send across food and booze.
If you need anything else,
give me a shout, I'll come over.
Hey, I'm not able to reach Arasu, Bro!
-Saami, did he speak to you?
-The money is in this bag.
He called me the day before
and asked to collect the money.
After that, he didn't call me either.
I hope it includes my commission.
At least give me an advance,
I'll sort it out.
Hey, I can't settle your account now.
Once the work is done,
we'll split the money.
If you go back on your word
and do not pay me my commission
I'll get violent!
Hey!
Did you get him?
What is it, Chunnilal?
-Big deal is going down.
-Okay.
-Border crossing!
-What about it?
-Also, there's a girl here.
-Entrusting you?
I'm the guardian of women.
Hey, you brought that girl along.
What are you planning to do?
I spoke to Saami.
He will handle it.
-I'll be back in a minute.
-I wonder what you spoke about.
I'll speak to them.
[in Hindi] I'll speak to them.
Don't worry.
What are you blabbering in Telugu?
-Telugu, you say?
-It isn't?
Moron! I'm speaking in Hindi.
Okay.
-Bear this in mind.
-What?
Chunnilal-Chandra.
Okay.
Don't our names match?
-What is it?
-Social service.
-Go to a corner and continue.
-Okay.
We're leaving in the morning.
Good job, three square meals,
and a place to stay.
Take it as your rebirth
and live a good life.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I still have time until dawn to decide.
Brother, give me a cigarette.
All units move in!
What happened?
Nothing!
How much money is in there?
There are 10 lakhs in the bag.
What happened out there?
Kitty!
-Hey, Kitty!
-What happened?
They killed Arasu Bro.
-What are you saying?
-They killed Arasu Bro.
They killed Arasu?
-It's out in the paper.
-Wait a minute, let's verify.
What's his name?
Arokiadoss, call him.
I feel something's not right.
If they had killed Arasu,
they would've found us too.
-Are you serious?
-What do we do now?
Did you notice anything unusual?
Hey, please say something.
-I don't understand.
-What are you doing?
Hey!
Hey, run! Run!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
-Go! Go! Go!
-Hey, how did they find us?
Hey, Das, this way!
Hey, pick him up.
-Pick him up.
-Kitty! Oh, no!
It's hurting like hell!
It's hurting!
Hey, come on!
Oh, no!
-Das!
-Get away from here.
Go!
-Hey, don't!
-Don't shoot!
Chandra run!
Come on, Kitty! Come on!
-Get inside the car.
-Keep moving, Chandra!
Hey, come on!
-Give me bullets.
-Hold it.
You go ahead.
Chandra, come with me.
Hey, Chandra.
Hey, Chandra, keep running.
-Das!
-Chandra, you come, Das will follow.
Come with me!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Hey, come on! Let's go, Das.
-Where are they?
-Hold on! They'll be here!
-Das!
-Come on, Das! Come on, Das!
Come on, hurry up!
-Hurry up!
-Come on, get in!
Get in! Get in!
-Start the vehicle.
-Come on, drive!
Did you kill Bhojraj or not?
Das! Two bullets got me.
Nothing will happen to you.
Shut up!
Hey, two bullets, Kitty.
-Switch on the light.
-I know it hit me.
Hey, why are you switching on the light?
-Where's the money?
-Two bullets!
-Where is the money?
-Hey, where the hell is the bag?
I'm scared I'm going to die.
And you're worried about the bag,
you mental.
-Turn around the car.
-The hell, I won't turn around.
-I'm not ready to die.
-We can't leave without the money.
Hey, we can't go back.
If you turn around, I'll kill you.
Life is more important than money.
You're mad to turn around.
Hey, shut up, damn it!
-Drive faster and switch off the lights.
-Okay.
Two bullets.
Hey!
Hey, Kitty, two bullets hit me.
-Hey, Kitty!
-Stop screaming.
-Come in.
-Das, two bullets hit me.
-I know it, Das.
-Hey, Chunnilal!
-It's hurting, Das.
-Everyone you bring is always weird.
You lost the money
and are now wincing in pain.
-[in Hindi] Shut up, damn it.
-Shut up and keep walking.
[muffled voice] Kitty, two bullets.
It's hurting, Das.
-Hey, you must leave before dawn.
-Okay.
-Kitty, two bullets.
-Here!
-This way.
-Get in.
Kitty, why don't you understand?
Hey, quickly sit down.
Kitty!
Hey! Hey!
-Shut up and sit down.
-It's hurting. Two bullets, damn it!
-I saw, Das.
-Calm down.
I saw, Das.
-Two bullets, Das.
-Don't switch on the phone.
-I'm done for good.
-Damn you!
-Please do something about him.
-I lost my hand.
I'm done! I'm scared, Das.
Two bullets, Das. Das!
Das!
It's hurting, Das!
It was just one bullet.
It went in and out clean.
There's no bullet lodged inside.
Freakin', shut your gob and calm down.
Hey, I don't care about the money.
It's a big deal that we are alive now.
First, let's leave this town.
I won't leave until I deliver
the money to Angani's son.
What?!
Have you lost your mind?
They killed Arasu.
And we're next to go.
Let's go to Andhra.
Shut up and leave.
If you're scared, you may leave.
I won't stop you.
Do you want money?
What did you say?
Who the hell is she?
Yes, we need money.
Do you have it?
Why is she even tagging along?
In the morning,
take me to the place I tell you.
What? Where?
There's a Kannan Lodge
near the Erode bus stand.
Yes, it's out there.
-Owner?
-Over there.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
"Move to the rhythm
Dance all night"
Of the beat beat"
Kitty, let me have a drink.
I can't bear the pain.
Hey, Karuppu, stay quiet,
else I'll kill you.
Here you go!
Hey, check how much is in there.
How did you manage to get the money?
Everything has a price.
Dignity has a price too.
How much is in there?
It'll be around 3 lakhs.
But it's not enough.
Take me to Jackson Textiles
in Erode Bazaar.
Yes!
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
Hey, she's out. She's out.
She's freaking hot!
" Move to the rhythm
Dance all night "
Of the beat beat "
" Move to the rhythm
Dance all night "
Of the beat beat "
" Move to the rhythm
Dance all night "
Won't that flower wither?
It's plastic.
Just like me.
But one thing is evident.
Like a thief stung by a scorpion,
they're sparing no expense
to save their honor.
It's working for us.
-I'll tell you the truth.
-Go ahead. Let me hear it.
So, Chandra...
New clothes and money wherever you go.
[in Hindi] What a wow!
I would rather have been born a sex worker.
I could've made a lot of money.
What's next?
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
A-1 Pandian Hotel.
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
Count it!
Damn, that's a lot of money.
K2-Police station, Sub-inspector.
Hey, we cannot go inside
the police station.
Das, she won't leave
until she gets us killed.
We can't do anything
when he's at the station.
We could kidnap him from his house.
Hey, get in!
Hey, drive! Drive, drive!
" Move to the rhythm
Dance all night "
What you have in mind
isn't going to happen.
How do you know what's on my mind?
I know!
Just because she's bringing in money,
we can't keep her with us.
I thought you were crazy,
but she's crazier than you.
He's been longing for love
since he lost his mother as a child.
Two weeks ago,
before anything could happen
with the singer in Chennai
an unfortunate tragedy struck.
Her name was, ah,
Parvathy, from Coimbatore.
He's been torturing himself and
is feeling guilty about her death.
You become soft
when women are in trouble.
Be careful.
There's too much heat around.
Does she look like me?
You could say, though.
No wonder he's obsessed with it.
Whatever, we'll drop you off safely
on our way out.
You carry on with your life.
Forget about these guys.
Come with me.
Just the two of us...
Shall we go on a trip?
-What is your name?
-Chunnilal!
I'll snip the Lal!
" Move to the rhythm
Of the beat beat "
Dance all night "
-Is there enough?
-Yes, Das.
We got what we needed.
It's enough.
-There's one more to go.
-What?
We got the money.
Let's leave for Vellore.
This is the last one!
No need. Let's leave.
Das, it's just one more.
We've come all this way.
Why refuse when it's easy money?
Let's pick it up on our way out.
Kitty!
Hey, Silk, what are you doing here?
Das, the gun is missing.
Hey, be here, keep the engine running.
Hey, Kitty, check what's happening?
Start the car.
She got us into trouble.
Hey, Chunnilal, start the car.
Hey, stop gazing around.
Go and check, damn it!
What's wrong with you guys?
Sir, I swear I'm telling the truth.
They're going to
hand over the money in Vellore...
and cross-border to Andhra.
Also, there is a girl with them.
That's all I know, Sir.
So, you don't know for whom the money is?
I swear on my newlywed wife,
I don't know.
Hello?
Alert all the surrounding police stations.
They're still in Erode.
They killed a Doctor.
Listen, someone is heading over here.
-Who are you?
-Stay right there.
-What--?
-Stay calm. Don't scream.
How many people are here?
-Who else? How many are here?
-Only three of us.
Don't make a noise.
-Would anyone else be coming over?
-No one, Sir.
Das, come on!
-Stay silent. Don't scream.
-Go over there.
Put down your gun.
How many are out here?
It's just me, my wife, and the child.
We won't harm you.
Understand?
We will leave in the morning.
Stay quiet.
Hey, go around and check
if anyone else is around.
What's wrong with her?
She messed up everything.
Hey, move along.
Hey, around the back.
We'll leave by dawn.
We won't harm you, people.
Get inside.
Is anyone else out there?
-Did you check thoroughly?
-There's no one else.
Hey, why did you shoot him?
Why did you kill Kavarchi Kannan?
Didn't you say he kept you locked in?
So, I killed him.
Who permitted you to kill him?
Did you ask me?
Hey, why are you talking about
irrelevant stuff?
First, answer why you shot him?
You killed him because he did bad things.
I killed him because he did bad things.
When I told you I had no more desire
to become a mother...
you asked me why.
He ripped out my uterus when I was 16
looked in my face, laughed, and said
"You can never become a mother
in your life."
It wasn't just me...
all the girls over there
went through the same tragedy.
That's why I killed him.
Please tell me if I'm becoming
a problem to you people...
I'll go away from here.
-Hey, Chunnilal, walk faster.
-Shut up and follow me.
Hurry up, guys!
-Hey, hand me that bag.
-What is it?
-Hand me the bag!
-Hey, why are you inviting trouble?
-Hey, guys, hurry up!
-Here you go!
You carry on. I'll be back.
-Come on, Chandra.
-Where are you going?
-Hey, come with us.
-Go with them.
Move it, guys!
Hey, Chunnilal, go ahead,
he'll be back.
Keep him alive.
Do only what I ask you to do.
How long would it take
to go to Poonjolai station?
Approximately 9 hours, sir.
-Drive to Poonjolai.
-Okay, Sir.
Hey, you're the reason
the Police caught him.
You'll be responsible for his death.
That's it! They'll kill him for sure.
Don't show me your face.
Get lost!
Hey, Karuppu, let's leave.
Chandra, come with us.
I won't leave without Das.
Hey, why are you calling her?
-Hey, it's Das, damn it.
-So, what do you want me to do?
It's all done. He's doomed!
We can't do anything about it.
If one of you were caught by the Police
Das wouldn't have abandoned you.
She's right, Kitty.
We can't leave Das behind.
Earlier, we left Sebastian behind.
Next, it will be me.
Hey!
Bloody fate!
Let's go!
What's going on?
-How could you decide it yourself?
-This guy, I say.
The car is mine.
And I call the shots.
My job is to help you cross the border.
I can't rely on you and get shot in return.
However, there's a way around it.
What is it?
Do you want me?
Damn, this girl is very open about it.
First, help us.
Then I'll do whatever you ask me to.
Hey, come on!
Let's break him out.
[in Hindi] Never put off until tomorrow
what you can do today.
Come on!
Das has helped us a lot.
Get in the car. Let's go.
Hey, are you some big gangster?
Try escaping now.
I don't understand
why they want to keep you alive.
Die!
Hey, acting tough is it?
Acting tough is it? Is it?
You're killing the Police.
And she's killing the Doctor.
Damn you, people!
Is this a joke to you?
Come on, tell me!
Hey, what's her name?
Hey!
I'm asking you what her name is.
What's the name of that Fallen woman?
Hey, glaring at me, are you?
So, how does it work?
Does she make you happy?
Glaring at me?
I will ruin her in front of your eyes.
Hey, constable, bring me a condom.
Take it out.
Blast, Kitty!
Hey, who are you?
I won't let you die until I'm alive.
Come on! Come on!
Chunnilal, bring in the car.
Hurry up, get in!
Das?
-What is it?
-Das!
Her name is Chandra!
Not a Fallen woman!
Das, get out of there.
-Hey, drive away.
-Come on, Das!
Go! Go! Go!
"Eyes, don't fade away"
"The solace of your shadow... "
"Let the silence linger"
"As if I were your breath... "
-Bhojraj!
-Yes, Sir.
Despite the shoot-at-sight order,
why did you hold it?
You let him slip away again.
Because of you,
the station's inspector is dead.
Four other officers
are admitted to the hospital.
Bhojraj,
I'll give you 24 hours.
Das, his team,
and the new girl along with them...
kill them all.
He must not cross the border to Andhra.
Okay, Sir, I'll finish them all.
To hell with you!
Is surveillance still on Das's father?
Yes, Sir, we're on it.
-Manoj, Rajarishi.
-Sir!
You two take the local team's
support and trace in Erode.
Sure, Sir.
Ashraf and I are going to Vellore.
-I reckon he will come to meet his father.
-Yes, Sir.
Isn't family a weakness, Ashraf?
Let's go!
Hey, check if you could find a rod.
Wait!
Listen, he does not like you.
It's better if you leave.
I don't understand what's happening.
I'm feeling heavy.
She's an amazing girl.
Golden-hearted.
That's why I'm scared.
I lost many loved ones.
Hey, Das,
why are you thinking about the past?
She's considering you as her world.
In the morning, after you got caught...
Kitty wanted to leave right away.
But she stood her ground
and refused to leave without you.
I'll give you money.
Leave!
That's good for everyone.
That cheapo... Chunnilal.
He, too, wanted to leave.
But she somehow convinced him to help us.
She's a good girl.
Of course, she's a good girl.
How did she convince him?
Why don't you tell him everything?
Bear this in mind.
That girl will be the death of us.
I'm warning you guys.
Hey, how did she convince him?
You see... You see...
They don't know how to treat a woman.
Bloody hooligans!
That's why listen to me
and let go of them.
Anyhow, the Police will kill them all.
You cannot keep saving them like a hero.
They're not going to help you
cross the border.
I'm responsible for their safety.
Chandra...
Think about it.
You get involved with 10 men in a day.
But you haven't done it
for the past couple of days.
That's why you're upset.
Forget about everything.
We'll have fun.
We can have a lot of fun.
I have an elite list of clients.
We can earn in millions, Chandra.
Also, our deal is pending.
They will sleep in a while.
Just 10 minutes.
I'm enraged. Go away.
I'm freaking desperate.
I won't go.
You should leave.
Damn you, woman.
Once the work is done,
you're going back on your word.
Just because you wore a new saree...
won't make you a virtuous woman.
You're a Fallen woman!
Yes, Das!
As he helped you escape...
he wants me.
When I questioned?
He's calling me a Fallen woman.
Oh, no, Das! I did not say it.
I did not say anything like that.
Das, I did not say it.
In fact, I called her an angel.
But I think she misheard it.
Das, why would I do something like that?
Das! Das!
Either smoke it or put it back inside.
You've been tapping for a while now.
Do you know why I splattered
the Police officer's brain?
Except for you, everyone else
sees me in the wrong way.
Other than my name
what do you know about me?
For the past two days,
only you've been talking.
I know everything about you.
When you were young,
you lost your mother.
Your father does not talk to you.
You lost your friend Sebastian.
Parvathy's death in Madras.
You're afraid I, too, might die.
I know a lot, though.
Beyond everything, are you contemplating
because of what I was before?
That's one thing I don't know about you.
Don't talk nonsense.
That's not what I am thinking about.
So, it's the fear.
When the Police caught you...
I was scared I might not see you again.
As Kitty suggests, let's drop everything,
go far away, and live a reformed life.
I wish to live my life with you, Das.
Hey, let's quit everything.
We'll find another job.
We'll think about killing Bhojraj.
All sounds good. Let's go.
But not with her.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
Leave her here.
Let's not bring her along.
I'm not coming without her.
You don't have to come.
We are leaving.
-Hey, Kitty!
-Shut up, damn it!
Don't test my patience
Already, a girl died because of you.
Yet you want to bring her along.
-Kitty!
-I don't wish to die because of her.
I'm not ready for it.
You may stick together.
We're going our way.
Why are you glaring at me?
Why?
Hey!
It's not only your life,
but also our lives are at stake.
-Why are you speaking indifferently?
-Shut up, damn it!
-Don't speak like a crazy person.
-He won't leave her behind.
He's panicking
if something happens to her.
Hey!
Listen, I'm saying it.
She's a Fallen woman!
Try denying it!
-Hey, don't speak ill about a woman.
-Kitty, don't!
Take your hands off me.
I'm saying it to your face.
She's a Fallen woman!
-How are you?
-Das, calm down!
What else do you expect me to say?
Hey! Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Hey, shut up. Stop screaming.
-Das!
-Hereafter, I'm everything to you.
-Stop the car!
-I'll take care of you.
Karuppu! Karuppu!
-Hey, stop the car!
-They won't make it out alive.
-Stop!
-I won't stop the car.
Hey, crazy woman.
Don't you hear me, woman?
How dare you?
Chandra!
Why don't you agree to get out
of here and earn more money?
Enough with your theatrics!
Das is sweet in your eyes,
but I'm bitter, right?
Freaking Chunnilal!
Das!
Kitty, hear me out.
-Wait! Wait!
-Let go of me.
We need him alive.
Please hear me out.
Let go of me!
Karuppu!
-Das!
-Karuppu!
Das!
Okay, Sir. Sure, Sir.
Why are you being so egoistic
with your son?
I, too, have a son.
He was dancing to his wife's tunes.
Lately, all sons have become the same.
I fulfilled every responsibility
I could as a father.
His one mistake ruined everything.
I'm enraged, you know.
I'm not going to cross the border
until I kill them all.
Kitty, you better leave.
Try to live a good life.
After this, a reformed life
doesn't make sense to me.
I won't leave
until I have killed everyone.
Even if it costs my life.
To avoid sharing wealth
with their sister...
my brother-in-laws tried to
betray my wife.
But my wife is a headstrong woman.
She didn't let it go.
She threatened to go to court.
Do you know what they did?
They hacked down their sister
and brutally killed her.
I was enraged.
Don't I know how to pick up the sickle
and kill them all?
But I did not do it.
Do you know why?
Because my son was 13-14 years old.
I suppressed my anger...
borrowed money
and provided him with education.
Why?
If he studies well,
he'll help me in the future.
Did he come through?
He was determined to avenge his
mother's death and killed his uncles.
Why the heck
should I still provide him education?
You have decided to kill them.
But before, deliver the money
where it belongs.
Also, meet your father.
I agree,
you have every right to be angry.
But this is too much ego!
Pick up the phone and speak to him.
He called you
because he's long to speak to you.
The Police will be watching my father.
Let him mind his business.
No good can come of talking to him.
I'm more egoistic than you are.
Because he spoke against me...
I stopped seeing him for good.
Yet you're advising me.
Where is your son now?
Hello.
Yes, Son.
After getting married,
he had a child and lived a good life.
Later, he didn't want to do
anything with me or my wealth.
Pride!
In the end,
he sold his agricultural land
but I got a news
that he never returned with the money.
My daughter-in-law is sure he stopped
at the checkpost to help the police.
I did question the Police.
They said, "He'll return home
once he runs out of money."
And branded him a drunkard!
They didn't even file
a missing person case.
We consulted many lawyers
and police, but in vain.
Get out of here.
I'm warning you!
If you don't leave,
I'll book you under a brothel case.
If the police behave like this,
who do we go to for help?
-Hey, get out of her.
-Oh, no!
Get out!
Take them away from here.
I was suffering in pain without knowing
if he was alive or dead.
But the anger festering inside me
refused to spare them.
That's when I went to your son,
explained everything,
and identified them.
Are you saying
that you know my son?
I know your son better than you.
When a crime is committed,
the police step in to solve it.
But when the police themselves commit
a crime, who'd step in to question it?
Sir!
They're hiding out
in an old paper mill near a quarry.
We have surrounded them.
Get here soon, Sir.
Okay!
Ashraf, quickly start the car.
Alert the entire team.
They're at the old paper mill.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I need backup.
They only listen to affluent people.
They don't even consider us
as human beings.
But if you treat them as they deserve
and question they'll listen.
Your son questioned them!
Hey!
Come on!
Hello, inform the local station.
Come on, get in the car.
They killed my son
and threw him in the bushes.
In the end,
I saw only my son's corpse.
Go! Go! Go!
Did you say you struggled to
provide an education for your son?
My son, too, sold all his wealth
to support his son's education.
We lost that money as well.
False pride!
I'm a father.
Why should I let go of my ego?
I held on to it.
Now I feel like talking to my son.
But my son is no more to talk to.
Sir, please come.
Sure, Son.
You keep the motor to yourself.
Your son is here. Talk to him.
-I brought a bag.
-It's okay. You can keep it.
Study well!
-Go safe.
-Bye, Son.
I called you many times.
You didn't answer.
Dad, are you never going to
talk to me again?
Why should I even talk to you?
I warned you enough.
But you didn't pay heed to me
and ruined everything.
-What's left to talk about anymore?
-You should've spoken, Dad.
You should've spoken!
You should've knocked
some sense into me with it.
Who knows!
I may have listened to you.
Girl! Who are you?
How could you trust him?
I'm his father.
Look at my condition.
Please be smart
and take care of your life.
You think you're off the radar.
The Police have tracked you down.
First, find a way to vacate this shop.
I know how to take care of myself.
Do what you came for
and be on your way.
"I break away... "
"I don’t obey"
Bomb!
"I break away... "
"I don’t obey"
I don't know why.
But I wanted to see you one last time.
Not sure
If I were to get another chance.
So, are you done?
If I escape from the Police and return
let's try to live as father and son.
Fine, we'll try to make it happen.
"I break away..."
"I don’t obey"
Das, make it fast!
"I break away..."
Hey!
He's on top!
You check upstairs!
Hey, Kitty!
Did you take a bullet?
Even when I'm about to die
you're late.
I thought you guys wouldn't come.
How could I not come for you?
Hey!
I won't rest until I kill you,
damn it!
Dad!
-Ameena! Ameena!
-What happened, Dad?
-How are you, dear?
-Why do you sound weird?
-Did you eat?
-Dad, where are you?
How is your mother?
Dad, when will you come home?
Dad!
-Dad, what happened?
-I'll come soon.
Dad!
I'll be home soon.
Dad! What happened, Dad?
Dad, can you hear me?
Dad, what's that sound?
Dad, say something.
Can you hear me?
Dad! Dad, what's happening?
Dad!
Dad, say something.
Dad, can you hear me?
Dad, what happened?
When will you return home?
Dad! Dad!
Dad, can you hear me?
Dad, say something.
Dad...
Dad, please say something.
I'm very scared, Dad.
Dad, say something.
Dad!
-Your Dad...
-Uncle!
and a few policemen are hurt.
Send an ambulance
to the Vellore paper mill.
Uncle, who are you?
What happened to my Dad, Uncle?
What happened to my Dad--?
-Kitty, what happened?
-Nothing's wrong.
Hey, take care of him.
Hey!
Where are you planning to go?
It's a huge world.
Das!
As long as she's with you, you're safe.
Let's go, Kitty!
We're still listed as rowdies, gangsters,
and extremists in the police files.
They've written our destiny,
and it cannot be altered.
But we stopped running
to discover who we truly are.
With faith that education
will shape Angani's son,
even this lifeless plastic flower
and this death-dealing gun,
as my mother says,
will send you into this vast world
to build a life.
www.1TamilMV.meme